{
    "id": "9010325b3f144463987e8b22df457618",
    "title": "Concession And Contrast",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "....................................... working hard, he couldn’t pass the test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Although",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0bcec8c06abd47d8a5ffc93db27e8524"
        },
        {
            "question": "....................................... it was late, we decided to go out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "However",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "47dd0d6538674796acdda725cb92ba28"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................. being rich, she is not happy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "Although",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f78ae427523f47638e0c72d801e1a2e4"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................................. having a bad teacher, she passed her test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Although",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ba6515738ab2416caaa2be7cc5c14679"
        },
        {
            "question": "......................................... she lives next door, we rarely see each other.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "However",
                "Although",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f3fd44d907b54eb296dbadc2b3cd8b7f"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................... facing many setbacks, he didn’t lose hope.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "However",
                "In spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dd7f8d1ced784b34b58c4aef5a6127aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................ being a foreigner, she speaks English remarkably well.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "However",
                "Although"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "05eb94112cde4f048985ca9bec43ac3d"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................. she earns a good salary, she finds it difficult to make both ends meet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "However",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ba25143e513144c59aff1d29aa891b3f"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................................. living close to her office, she is always late for work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "However",
                "Though",
                "In spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0a5b6e9d56a84d2b9572af1997e4350f"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................................ working three jobs in a day, she makes it a point to spend quality time with her kids.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "However",
                "In spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "431e7b96ab574cf390aa707fe502db29"
        }
    ]
}